<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ASP Productions</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ASP Productions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 21:07:56 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>privacy</title>
      <link>/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 08:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/privacy/</guid>
      <description>The policy: This privacy policy notice is served by ASP under the website; [www.actorshop.co.uk]. The purpose of this policy is to explain to you how we control, process, handle and protect your personal information through the business and while you browse or use this website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>terms</title>
      <link>/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 08:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/terms/</guid>
      <description>Introduction These Website Standard Terms And Conditions (these “Terms” or these “Website Standard Terms And Conditions”) contained herein on this webpage, shall govern your use of this website, including all pages within this website (collectively referred to herein below as this “Website”).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Good to catch up with the lovely Jimmy Akingbola today at BAFTA</title>
      <link>/updates/update-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 21:07:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/updates/update-one/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking forward to Talawa Firsts 2019: Fresh Black Voices - Innovative - Electrifying - Unapologetic - at the Ditch at Shoreditch Town Hall to celebrate the UK&#39;s most exciting new Black writers and theatre makers from 19th June to 5th July 2019.</title>
      <link>/updates/update-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 23:05:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/updates/update-four/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jonny Wright</title>
      <link>/testimonials/jonny-wright/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/testimonials/jonny-wright/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve had a great relationship with first Pampaset and now Actorshop. Through them I got my first film and then television development deals and without their support, I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I&amp;rsquo;d still be writing today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great to see Leeds Playhouse will be staging a new production of Hanif Kureishi’s iconic and Oscar-nominated screenplay MY BEAUTIFUL LAUNDRETTE</title>
      <link>/updates/update-six/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 08:41:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/updates/update-six/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Great table reading of WILD ALICE by Hanif Kureishi.  Brilliant script and a fabulous cast.  Thank you to all who were present for your contributions! </title>
      <link>/updates/update-five/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 08:37:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/updates/update-five/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patricia Elcock</title>
      <link>/people/patricia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 17:23:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/patricia/</guid>
      <description>Patricia Elcock has worked with Actorshop for 15 years. She began as an actor/facilitator before moving into the company’s management team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don Warrington</title>
      <link>/people/don/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 17:23:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/don/</guid>
      <description>Warrington is known for playing Philip Smith in Rising Damp, from 1974 to 1978, alongside Leonard Rossiter, Richard Beckinsale, and Frances de la Tour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Derek Brown</title>
      <link>/people/derek/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 17:11:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/people/derek/</guid>
      <description>Derek started his production career in 1985 as part of the creative team for Danny’s Big Night a film exploring young men and women’s attitudes towards contraception in the mid-1980s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Search for Writers</title>
      <link>/about/our-search-for-writers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 16:36:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/our-search-for-writers/</guid>
      <description>If you feel passionately a story should be told, we’d like to have a read. We don’t want more than an A4 setting out the idea and promise to get back to you promptly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/about-us/</guid>
      <description>Triple BAFTA Award winners, Actorshop, have merged with Pampaset to form ASP productions with a vision of producing popular work that reflects and celebrates the diversity of modern Britain, for television and film.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archie Maddox</title>
      <link>/testimonials/archie-maddox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/testimonials/archie-maddox/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Writing is one of those weird processes that you can’t really explain why you have to do it. I don’t think anyone chooses to be a writer, you kind of just are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carlo Kureishi</title>
      <link>/testimonials/carlo-kureishi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/testimonials/carlo-kureishi/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Before meeting Derek and Don I had only vague ambitions of becoming a screenwriter. Like anyone interested in writing films and television shows, I&amp;rsquo;d started with the how-to books; playing with scenes and characters, dialogue and structure, hoping something great might accidentally come out of me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trish Cooke</title>
      <link>/testimonials/trish-cooke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/testimonials/trish-cooke/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I had the pleasure of working with Actorshop, as a writer, a few years ago whilst developing a children’s TV drama idea with them for CBBC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Very much looking forward to STRANGE FRUIT by Caryl Phillips at the Bush.  Wonderful to see this production coming back!</title>
      <link>/updates/update-seven/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/updates/update-seven/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>